conservativehome.com 2019-12-08

# Privacy Policy | Conservative Home

## PRIVACY AND LEGAL

This privacy policy sets out how ConservativeHome collects and uses any information you may give us when you visit this website, as well as how we may disclose that information, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of that information.

Your privacy is our priority and we go to great lengths to protect it. Any information we collect about you will always be handled securely and in compliance with the UK Data Protection Act (1998), the forthcoming General Data Protection Regulation (EU2016/679) and all other relevant legislation.

We will never sell, rent, share, or otherwise disclose your personal information to anyone except to provide our services or as otherwise described in this policy, without providing explicit notice of such and the ability to opt out.

## POLICY APPLICATION

This privacy policy applies to information provided to us by, or collected from, visitors to our websites and users of our services.

Other websites to which we provide links most likely have their own privacy policies which we would strongly encourage you to read.

## DATA COLLECTION

ConservativeHome is the owner of the service information collected on this website and through any related service. As visitors browse our website, or use our services, we normally log this activity to provide a better service to our users.

We may store, collect and use any personal information you provide to us, either directly or otherwise, that enables you to make use of our services. This may include your name, email address and postcode. This also includes information about any donations your might make or advocacy actions you may take part in.

This also includes where you might ‘follow’, ‘like’ or otherwise link your social media accounts to our services via a third-party website. Any correspondence you send electronically may be retained, such as the content of your email messages, your email address and our response. We may also retain any information you upload or post on this website such as profile pictures and comments.

We only collect the information that we need to fulfil the purposes set out at collection. You can update this information at any time.

## DATA USE

The information you provide may be used to help you make use of our services, to respond to your queries, and to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of this website and our services. You may opt out from receiving such information at any time.

In order for us to provide our services we may provide information that you supply to us to our affiliates, vendors and service providers, which we may use for billing, customer support and other technical operations. In all such cases, we will ensure that such entities are bound by appropriate confidentiality restrictions to protect the information covered by this policy.

We will never use or share personal information that you provide to us in ways unrelated to those described herein. For clarity, personal data will never be rented or sold to third parties, including any commercial or political entity.

## COOKIES

Our site and services use cookies in order to provide a better service to you. Cookies are placed by a browser onto your computer’s hard drive to assign a unique identification to that computer.

For example, we may use cookies to help direct you to the appropriate part of our website, by indicating that you are a repeat visitor to our website. We may also use information provided to us to present you with services that are customised to your preferences. ConservativeHome does not store information we consider personal or private in a cookie, unless that information is obscured.

Some portions of our website are functional without cookies. You may delete our cookies yourself through your browser’s cookie manager. However, disabling cookies will reset your session and may adversely affect other functions on the ConservativeHome website and the services we provide.

By using our website or services, you are consenting to our use of cookies in accordance with this notice. If you do not agree to our use of cookies then we advise you to set your browser settings accordingly.

You can find out more about cookies at allaboutcookies.org.

## DATA AGGREGATION

ConservativeHome may aggregate data we acquire about our users and visitors to our websites. For example, we may assemble data to determine how visitors interact with our services, and whether they are engaged in malicious activity. If we assemble this sort of data and provide it to external parties, our users’ personal information will never be attached to or included in such aggregated data.

## LEGAL OBLIGATIONS

We may be required by law, court order, or other legal process to provide information about our users to outside parties. It’s our policy to ensure adherence to the due process of law in all such instances, and if we are required to provide information under these circumstances, we will, whenever possible, attempt to inform users whose information we are compelled to produce, unless prohibited by law.

To date, we have never received such a request.

## DATA SECURITY

We take all reasonable steps to protect information we receive from our users from loss, misuse or unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration and / or destruction. We’ve put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure such information. ConservativeHome only processes personal information in a way that is compatible with and relevant for the purpose for which it was collected or authorised.

We allow our users and our website visitors access to their own personal information, and allow them to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate personal information, except where the burden or expense of providing such access is disproportionate to the individual privacy risk, or where the rights of persons other than the requesting individual risk being violated.

## DATA TRANSFER

Our systems, services and the data therein are based on servers that reside either within the United Kingdom or the Republic of Ireland. Some third party providers may necessarily require data to be transferred outside of the EEA to the United States. Regardless, any transfers will only be made where we are satisfied that the systems are secure and fully compliant with this policy.

Accessing or using our sites or services, or otherwise providing information to us, constitutes consenting to our potential transfer, processing and storage of such information in the United States.

## DATA CONTROL

ConservativeHome is a registered data controller (#ZA335169) with the UK Information Commissioner’s Office.

If the information we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated, you would like to be unsubscribed from our services, or have any other questions or concerns about our use of your personal data, please contact us at privacy@ConservativeHome.com 

To request a copy of any information we hold about you, please send proof of identity to privacy@ConservativeHome.com which we will respond to within 40 days.

Further to the disclosures identified elsewhere in this policy, we will only disclose personal information to third parties if required by law to do so.

## POLICY UPDATES

While we don’t anticipate this policy to broadly change, any modifications or updates required – most likely as a result of new products or services, or updated legal frameworks – will be posted on this website along with the effective date of any changes.

This policy was last updated 3rd April 2018

## CONTACT INFORMATION

This website is operated by ConservativeHome (#07053162), a company limited by guarantee in England and Wales, whose registered office is 21 Marina Court, Castle Street, Hull, HU1 1TJ.

You can contact us in writing at the above address or via email at privacy@ConservativeHome.com
